const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'What position did Zinedine Zidane play?',
      answers: [
        'striker',
        'left winger',
        'playmaker',
        'leftback'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'playmaker',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many goals did Zidane score in the 1998 World Cup Final?',
      answers: [
        '0',
        '1',
        '2',
        '3'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '2',
    },
    {
      question: "What is Zinedine Zidane's nickname?",
      answers: [
        'El Fenomenon',
        'Magic Chris',
        'The King',
        'Zizou'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Zizou',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which team did Zidane never play for?',
      answers: [
        'Algeria',
        'France',
        'Juventus',
        'Bordeaux'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Algeria',
    }, 
    {
      question: 'How many Champions League trophies did he win as a player',
      answers: [
        '0',
        '1',
        '2',
        '3'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '1',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many Champions League trophies did he win as a manager',
      answers: [
        '0',
        '1',
        '2',
        '3'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '3',
    },
    {
      question: "How many Ballon d'Or and FIFA player of the year awards does Zidane have?",
      answers: [
        '1',
        '2',
        '3',
        '4'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '4',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which was his last competitive match?',
      answers: [
        '2001 Champions league final',
        '2006 final La Liga game',
        'Euro 2004 semin-final',
        '2006 World Cup final'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '2006 World Cup final',
    },
    {
      question: "What is Zidane's signature move called?",
      answers: [
        'Panenka',
        'Pedalada step over',
        'La Roulette/the Marseille turn',
        'Elastico'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'La Roulette/the Marseille turn',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is my favorite player of all time?',
      answers: [
        'Lionel Messi',
        'Christian Ronaldo',
        'Luka Modric',
        'Zizou'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Zizou',
    }
];
